Guide to the Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection AIA.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection
1902-2017
1970-2001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Archives of Irish America
Kearns, Martin
Forde, Michael
Smyth, Treasa Goodwin
AIA.003
36.67 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 16 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, 9 oversize flat boxes, and 4 artifact boxes.
3.36 Gigabytes in 4 recordings
This collection documents the activities of Irish county societies in New York City. The organizations were first established in the late 1840s as social organizations, although later some groups began to intercede on behalf of evicted Irish tenants and offer benefits for sickness and death. Sports teams, especially hurling and Gaelic football, eventually became an important aspect of the societies. This collection consists of printed materials such as photographs, correspondence, circular letters, dinner journals, program flyers, meeting minutes, financial records, and other printed ephemera related to these societies' activities.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists primarily of printed materials such as circular letters, dinner journals and flyers related to the activities of Irish county societies based in New York City, dating mostly from the twentieth century. Dinner-dances, balls and events in conjunction with St. Patrick's Day, and activities of hurling and Gaelic football clubs are extensively documented in the collection.
All of the series contain journals and programs from dances and banquets. Of special note in the collection are Series XI: Fermanagh, XV: Kilkenny, and Series XXV: Roscommon. In addition to programs and journals, these series also contain financial records, correspondence, membership logs and information, and minutes. Photographs of social events, most unidentified, can be found in the Clare, Fermanagh and Roscommon series. Series XXVI: Sligo contains a published history of the County Sligo assocation in New York. Series VI: Cork contains a County Cork Flag filed with an obituary in remembrance of Dr. Maire Bradshaw, sister of the Mayor of Limerick and a Ph.D. in zoology and botany. Dr. Bradshaw held the position of Assistant Director of Scientific Research for the Helena Rubenstein Comsmetics Corporation in New York and later worked for New York City's Department of Health in the Bureau of Radiation Control.
Individual series exist for every county, even though the collection does not contain material representing each county.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in 32 series, listed alphabetically by county name. Files are arranged alphabetically within each series. Individual series have been created for each Irish county, even if there is no representative material in the collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Material in this collection was acquired from individual officers and members of particular county societies, was collected by archives staff, or came to the Archives as part of a larger collection. The accession numbers associated with this collection include 1997.008, 2010.036, 2012.028, 2017.025, 2018.116, 2019.103, and 2021.081.
In March 2025, Marion Casey donated an accretion; the accession number associated with this transfer is 2025.034. The Kerry Ladies Auxiliary uniforms were likely donated by Kathleen O'Sullivan in 2011.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Archives of Irish America Vertical File Collection (AIA 013) Gaelic Athletic Association (AIA 028) Ancient Order of Hibernians (AIA 046) United Irish Counties Association of New York (AIA 056) Emerald Societies of New York (AIA 057)
Historical Note
Irish county organizations were first organized in New York City in the late 1840s. The early societies were for the most part purely social organizations, but in the 1870s some started to offer benefits for sickness and death. Sports teams eventually became an important component of county organizations, especially hurling and Gaelic football clubs. In the 1880s, inspired by the land reform movement in Ireland, many additional county societies were organized. Evictions and high rents were often fought on a local basis in Ireland, and in New York a county society rather than one of the broader Irish fraternal or social organizations could often respond better or faster to sudden developments in the old country. In the early 1890s the first attempt was made to establish a central body to coordinate the Irish county societies; such an organization was set up in Manhattan and at the same time a similar coordinating body was formed in Brooklyn, where many county societies existed independently. Both of these overseeing bodies were similar in design to the present-day United Irish Counties Association (UICA), but after only a few years of work the early umbrella organizations went out of existence.
A detailed and informative history of county societies in New York by John T. Ridge, Mary McMullan and Mae O'Driscoll(from which the text above was excerpted and adapted) can be found on the UICA web site, at:
http://www.uicany.org/United_Irish_Counties/History.html
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
Some born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Custodial History
The Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association minute book was lent to New York University in 2017 for digitization as part of a project to digitize minute books belonging to Irish county societies in New York City. The minute book was returned to the Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association in 2019.
Appraisal
The following materials County Antrim from accession 2025.034 deaccessioned: a donation to County Antrim with checking account information; documentation of immigration legal case including information about circumstances of immigration and A-file#.
Correspondence.; Hurling (Game); Gaelic football.; Clippings (information artifacts); Souvenir programs.; Irish Americans -- Social life and customs.; Financial records; Minutes (administrative records); Ledgers (account books); Black-and-white photographs.; Irish Americans -- Societies, etc.; Irish Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Gilroy, John G.; Kearns, Martin; Forde, Michael; Smyth, Treasa Goodwin
- I. Antrim, 1951
  - County Antrim Society 13th Annual Ball program, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Ephemera and Photographs, 1953-2006 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- II. Armagh, 1979-2003
  - Armagh - Banquet and Dance Programs, 1969-1982 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Armagh - Charter, Constitution, and By-laws, undated, 1894, 1959 (Box Shared Tamiment 151, Folder 1)
  - Armagh - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Armagh - Member Ribbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Armagh - Newsletters and Meetings, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 11)
  - Armagh - Newspaper Clippings, 1981-2000 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Armagh - Panoramas, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 151, Folder 1)
  - Armagh - Photographs, 1930s, 1990s, undated (Box 56, Folder 9-11)
  - Armagh - Scrapbook, 1947-1993 (Box 57)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration / Victory Celebration Dance, 1999, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Anniversary Celebration, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Annual Dinner Dance, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Annual Dinner Dance, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Annual Outing [Panorama photograph], July 14, 1935 (Flat-file-folder 6, Tray 1)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Armagh Ball, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - County Armagh Association of New York Inc., Tomas O Fiaich Memorial Fund, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - County Armagh Donnelly Family Benefit Fund, circa 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - County Armagh Men's P&B Assocation of New York Dinner-Dance, 1979, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - County Armagh Men's P&B Assocation of New York Dinner-Dance Ticket and Program, 1924, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- III. Carlow, 1907-1999
  - Carlow Assocation of New York: Correspondence, 1957, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - County Carlow Assocation of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - County Carlow Men's Society Annual Ball, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - County Carlow Men's Social and Benevolent Association Minutes, Jan 1908-Jan 1918; cuid809 (Box 32)
  - Photograph and Clipping of Kathleen Cannon, 1957, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
- IV. Cavan, 1979-2005
  - The Breifne Review, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Gaelic Football and Social Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - County Cavan Women's Social and Benevolent Association, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Gaelic Football and Social Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gaelic Football and Social Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1998, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 1989, 1992, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 2000, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - P&B Association -- Cavan Football Team testimonial dinner-dance, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - P&B Assocation Inc. 150th Anniversary, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - West Cavan Reunion Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cavan Banner, undated; cuid34979 (Flat-file-folder cuid34979)
  - Cavan Ladies S&B Association Medal, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Ladies Cavan Uniform, undated (Box 58)
- V. Clare, 1945-1999
  - Assocation of Chicago Silver Anniversiary Dinner-Dance, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Clare Mens banner, 1950; cuid855; 1 item one banner (Roll-storage AIA.003.cuid855)
    Banners.
  - Dalcassian Scoial and Athletic Club Annual Dinner-Dance, 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football Club Annual Dinner-Dance, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hurling Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hurling Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hurling Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hurling Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hurling Club of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Senior Hurling Club Field Day and Games, Aug 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - International Tour, Dinner-Dance and Receptoin for the Clare Senior Hulring Team and Officials, Oct 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Association History, 1988, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Ball, Miscellaneous Materials, 1983-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1945-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Ads, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Ticket Sales, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Ticket Sales Check copies and notes, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Journal Ads, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Commemorative Book COmmittee, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Journal Adds, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Banquet Journal Adds, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Centennial Year Celebration, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Clippings, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Constitution and By-laws, 1966, 1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Darling Girl from Clare Festival, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Installation of Officers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Lovely Rose of Clare Pageant, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Mailing List, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Member's Dues Books, 1956-1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Property [Office inventory](Trustee Report), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Special Events, 1968, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Stationery, circa 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Claremens and Womens' Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: Annual Dinner-Dance Journals, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Claremens and Womens' Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association of New York City, Inc.: The Banner, 1963 (Box 2a, Folder 1)
  - Miltown Malbay Social Club of New York City, Inc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Lists and Ephemera, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: 100th Anniversary Ball, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
- VI. Cork, 1914-2016
  - Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association, 2005, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Annual Ball and Banquet, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Annual Ball, 1959, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Centennial Celebration Program, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Correspondence, 1984-1990, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association -- Diamond Jubilee, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association St. Patrick's Celebration Dinner-Dance, 1978, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association St. Patrick's Day Banquet, 1989, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association St. Patrick's Day Banquet, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Corkmen's Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association St. Patrick's Day Banquet, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 38)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association -- Banquet, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association of New York -- Dinner Dance, 2007 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association of New York Event Materials, 2013-2015 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1914-1921; cuid832 (Box 40, Volume 2)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1921-1927; cuid2603 (Box 41)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1927-1930; cuid833 (Box 39, Volume 3)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1930-1934; cuid834 (Box 40, Volume 1)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1934-1937; cuid835 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1938-1943; cuid840 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1943-1949; cuid836 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1950-1953; cuid837 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1953-1957; cuid838 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1965-1967; cuid839 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1971-1972; cuid841 (Box 39, Volume 1)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1972-1973; cuid842 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Minute Book, 1974-1978; cuid843 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association of New York souvenir journals, 2015-2016 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association Ladies Auxiliary Minute Book, 1947-1967; cuid844 (Box 39, Volume 2)
  - Flag: County Cork Flag and Obituary in remembrance of Dr. Maire Bradshaw, undated (Box 13a)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated (Box 23)
  - Cork Men's Banner, undated; cuid36286 (Box 52)
  - Cork Ladies Banner, undated; cuid34976 (Box 51)
  - Photographs, Remarks and By-laws for County Cork Benevolent, Patriotic and Protective Association, 1952-1966 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- VII. Derry, 1972-1989
  - Derry Society of New York Annual Bloody Sunday Memorial Mass, Jan 30, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Derry Society of New York -- Constitution, History, and Photographs, 1962-2005 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Derry Society Memorial March and Mass for Derry Thirteen, Feb 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Derry Society of New York Testimonial Dinner, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cap, undated (Box 66)
- VIII. Donegal, 1992-1996
  - A History of the Donegal Association Inc. of New York, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Donegal Association of New York, Inc.: Centennial Banquet, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Donegal Association of New York, Inc.: Membership Dues, 1966-1971 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Donegal Association of New York, Inc.: Minutes, 1961-1968 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
  - Donegal Association of New York, Inc. Irish Soldier Memorials, 1992, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Donegal Association of New York, Inc.: Photographs, Minutes, and Photocopies of Event Ephemera, 1961-1984 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Donegal Footbal Club of New York 46th Anniversary Gala Banquet, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated (Box 24)
- IX. Down
- X. Dublin, 1940-1999
  - Dublin Society of New York Annual Dinner-Dance, 1953-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13-14, Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 4)
  - Dublin Society of New York Annual St. Patrick's Day Dinner-Dance, 1948-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15, Box Shared Tamiment 016, Folder 7)
  - Dublin Society of New York mixed event photographs, 1940-1989 (Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 2-3, Box Shared Tamiment 030, Folder 10, Box 44, Folder 4, Box Shared Tamiment 016, Folder 6)
  - Dublin Society of New York -- The Dubliner, Event Ephemera, Photograph, 1953-1962 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- XI. Fermanagh, 1903-2001
  - Annual Dinner-Dances, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Annual Dinner-Dances, 1988-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Annual Dinner-Dances, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Ball of the Mens and Ladies Associations, Feb 1919 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, May 1903 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1931-1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Director John G. Gilroy, 1978-1998, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fermanagh Gaelic Football Commemorative Journal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Literature about Fermanagh, 1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1977-1996; cuid810 (Box 4, Folder 25)